buttersafe.com 2019-02-04

# Buttersafe » Privacy Policy

Buttersafe.com strives to provide clarity and transparency in matters related to the privacy of website visitors.

_____________________________  
**Advertising**

Buttersafe.com displays advertisements provided by third-party advertising networks. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services which may interest you. Links to each advertising network’s respective website and privacy policy are provided below:

  * [Adify](http://www.adify.com/) [[privacy policy](http://adify.com/privacy-policy)]
  * [Adtegrity](http://www.adtegrity.com/) [[privacy policy](http://www.adtegrity.com/about/privacy-policy/)]
  * [Advertising.com](http://www.advertising.com/) [[privacy policy](http://advertising.aol.com/privacy)]
  * [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/) [[privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)]
  * [Project Wonderful](http://www.projectwonderful.com/) [[terms of service (includes privacy policy)](http://www.projectwonderful.com/tos.php)]
  * [WebComics World](http://www.webcomicsworld.com/) [[privacy policy](http://www.comicspace.com/privacy.php)]

For general information on consumer privacy on the web as it pertains to advertising, you may wish to visit the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). The NAI also provides information and resources on [“opting-out” of behavioral advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

_____________________________  
**Analytics**

Buttersafe.com uses third-party analytics services to collect statistics about website visitors (for example, number of pageviews on a given day, or number of visits from a particular country during a given week). This information is used to determine the popularity of individual pages and sections. Links to each analytics service’s respective website and privacy policy are provided below:

  * [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) [[privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)]
  * [Quantcast](http://www.quantcast.com/) [[privacy policy](http://www.quantcast.com/privacy)] (Quantcast tags are used at the request of one of our ad providers, [Webcomics World](http://www.webcomicsworld.com/).)

_____________________________  
**Contacting Buttersafe**

If you have any questions related to this privacy statement, please contact us at the following email address: buttersafe (at) gmail (dot) com.
